

## SAH KWADWO DANIEL

Full Stack Website and Mobile Application Developer



danielsah118@outlook.com



+233 545143000



Techiman, Bono East

#### **ABOUT ME**

Resourceful Full stack developer bringing in-depth knowledge of latest technology trends to produce superb web and mobile applications. Experience handling complex designs and algorithms to meet organization's needs. Detail-oriented with others to define project expectations and demands.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2018 - Present

### Website and Mobile App Developer | Self Employed | Techiman

Write clean code, integrating design, extensions and third-party apps according to development pans.

Test site compatibility across multiple browsers and devices, uncovering and debugging issues and addressing inconsistencies

2021 - 2023

#### Sales Agent | MTN aYo | Techiman

- Provide superior service to customers by quickly and courteously responding to requests, inquiries, suggestions and concern.
- Offer each customer top-notch, personal service to boost sales and customer satisfaction

## **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

Bsc. Computer Science | University of Energy and Natural Resources, Sunyani 2020 - 2024

2014 - 2017**General Science | Armed Forces Senior High Technical School, Kumasi** 

### **SKILLS**

HTML and CSS proficiency MongoDB

React MySQL

Nodejs / Express.js Responsive Web Development

**React Native** Python

# PERSONAL SKILLS

Leadership and Training

Creativity

Planning and Forecasting

Ability to work under pressure

**Great Problem Solving Ability** 

# **LANGUAGES**

English

French

# **SOCIAL LINKS**



https://github.com/Danny-Quan



www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-sah-kwadwo-9a79271a6

Portfolio website: <a href="https://dannyquan.netlify.app/">https://dannyquan.netlify.app/</a>